## Catie Tortorella

San Diego, CA

541-951-3504

catietortorella@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/catietortorella

github.com/CatieTort

Summary

Full stack web developer with a passion for clear and effective communication using proven methods based on research. I hope to creatively solve problems using web development and knowledge of usability to provide technology that is easy for humans to use.

Skills

- Javascript
- HTML & CSS
- React
- PostgresSQL
- Sequelize
- Express.js
- Bootstrap
- Jest
- RESTful APIs
- Agile/SCRUMTest Driven Development
- Dair Dragramming
- Pair Programming
- Google Analytics
- Git
- Github
- Word
- PowerPoint
- Excel

Photoshop

Catie.codes

- SendGridFirebase
- i ilebase
- MailChimp
- Streamsend

Experience

Web Developer Intern, *DoWhop*; La Jolla, CA – 2018 - current

- Built user profile image upload and display feature using JavaScript and Firebase cloud functions
- Using SendGrid API built automated Email feature using Firebase cloud functions
- Provided usability review of current site and implemented bug fixes
- Analyzed legacy code and improved code architecture
- Assisted with co-sponsored networking and promotion event

Executive Assistant, Middleton Team Inc. - Pete Knows Real Estate Team; La Jolla, CA - 2015-2017

- Strategically prioritized, scheduled, and managed all incoming appointments
- Point of contact for clients selling multi-million dollar homes
- Supported clients and agents in the home buying and selling process; generated \$172 Million in sales over 2.5 years
- Created of web and print marketing materials for home listings
- Initiated and compiled client listing, purchase, and negotiation contracts

Customer Service & Project Representative, CenterWatch; Boston, MA - 2010-2014

- Troubleshooted and cultivated online and print subscriptions for 5,000 subscribers
- Improved web content partnership outreach, increased participation by 30% within 18 months
- Increased efficiency of email campaigns with subscriber update initiative; decreased email bounces by 40% over 13 months
- Generated monthly analytic report on web traffic and subscriber trends
- Liaised with various departments to implement new strategies based on analytic report
- Created an advertising cost analysis as part of a targeted marketing strategy
- Interviewed and trained new hires on internal systems, including leadership

Education

University of Massachusetts Amherst, Amherst, MA – B.A. in Communications

Certified Polysomnographic Technician (CPSGT) California Real Estate License CalBRE: 02011558